http://www.universal-textiles.com/pages/privacy-policy

Submit
Close search
Reviews
ORDER WITH CONFIDENCE - WE'RE DELIVERING AS USUAL!Login Create Account Close MenuBrands TrespassFruit Of The LoomRegattaCraghoppersDare 2BResultGildanSOLSBeechfieldCaterpillarSkechersPremierFlosoAwdisRiva HomeRussellBagbaseMirakCotswold(Show All)Men ClothingFleecesHoodies & SweatshirtsJackets & CoatsJumpers & CardigansPolo ShirtsPyjamas & NightwearShirtsShortsSocksSuit Jackets & BlazersSwimwearTrousersT-Shirts & VestsUnderwearFootwearBootsFlip Flops & SandalsTrainersShoesSlippersAccessoriesBagsBeltsGlovesHandkerchiefsHatsJewelleryKeyringsPhone Cases & AccessoriesScarvesSunglassesTiesUmbrellasWalletsWomen ClothingDressesFleecesHoodies & SweatshirtsJackets & CoatsJumpers & CardigansPolo ShirtsPyjamas & NightwearShirts & BlousesShortsSkirtsSocks & TightsSuit Jackets & BlazersSwimwearTrousersT-Shirts & VestsUnderwear & LingerieFootwearBootsFlip Flops & SandalsHeelsTrainersShoesSlippersAccessoriesBagsBeltsCompact MirrorsGlovesHatsJewelleryPhone Cases & AccessoriesPursesScarvesSunglassesUmbrellasBoy ClothingFleecesHoodies & SweatshirtsJackets & CoatsPolo ShirtsPyjamas & NightwearShirtsSocksSwimwearTrousersT-Shirts & VestsUnderwearFootwearBootsFlip Flops & SandalsTrainersShoesSlippersAccessoriesBagsGlovesHatsPencil CasesPlush ToysScarvesSunglassesUmbrellasGirl ClothingDressesFleecesHoodies & SweatshirtsJackets & CoatsPolo ShirtsPyjamas & NightwearShirts & BlousesSocks & TightsSwimwearTrousersT-Shirts & VestsUnderwearFootwearBootsFlip Flops & SandalsTrainersShoesSlippersAccessoriesBagsGlovesHatsPencil CasesPlush ToysScarvesSunglassesUmbrellasBaby Baby BoysAll-In-Ones & BodysuitsHoodies & SweatshirtsJackets & CoatsPyjamas & NightwearSets & OutfitsShoes & BootiesSocksSwimwearTrousersT-Shirts & VestsBaby GirlsAll-In-Ones & BodysuitsDressesHoodies & SweatshirtsJackets & CoatsPyjamas & NightwearSets & OutfitsShoes & BootiesSocksSwimwearTrousersT-Shirts & VestsBaby Accessories & BeddingBibsBlanketsChanging MatsGloves & MittensHatsTowelsSport MensAccessoriesBase LayersJacketsShortsSocks & UnderwearFootwearTrousersT-Shirts & TopsWomensBase LayersGlovesJacketsShortsSocks & UnderwearFootwearTrousersT-Shirts & TopsBoysAccessoriesBase LayersGlovesJacketsShortsSocks & UnderwearFootwearTrousersT-Shirts & TopsGirlsBase LayersGlovesJacketsShortsSkirtsSocks & UnderwearTrousersT-Shirts & TopsMerchandiseBagsBeddingClothing & FootwearGolf AccessoriesFlagsKeyrings & JewelleryMugs & GlassesTowelsToysUmbrellasWalletsAccessoriesCycling AccessoriesEquestrian AccessoriesFootball AccessoriesHome Soft FurnishingsChair Backs & SlipcoversCurtainsCushions & CoversDoorstopsRugs & Floor MatsHome AccessoriesOrnamentsPlaques & SignsBedroomBed SheetsBlankets & ThrowsDuvet CoversPillows & PillowcasesBathroomBath MatsShower CurtainsTowelsKitchenLunch Boxes & Water BottlesMugs & CupsTableclothsTea TowelsWork Industrial & Hi-VisibilityAccessoriesFootwearGlovesJacketsOverallsShortsTrousersT-Shirts & TopsCateringAccessoriesApronsJacketsTrousersHealth, Medical & BeautyJacketsTrousersTunics & TopsSale Reduced to ClearAll Sale
100,000+ Products
Price Promise
Free Delivery Over £50
Reviews
Privacy Policy
What is this Privacy Policy for?
This privacy policy is for this website www.universal-textiles.com and served by Universal Textiles UK Ltd and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it.
The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations & requirements of the users, the website and website owners. Furthermore the way this website processes, stores and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy.
What information we collect, why and how we use it?
Universal Textiles will not collect or use any information not necessary to fulfilling your order.
Type of Information
How and why we use it
Name, Address & Date of Birth
Fulfill the delivery of your orderFraud prevention checks
Contact Details(Email Address, Phone Number, etc)
Communication of order updates and marketing information (where explicitly requested by you)
Payment Details
Take paymentProvide refundsFraud prevention checks
Contact History(Emails, letters, etc)
Provide customer supportStaff training
Purchase History
To complete transactionsProvide customer supportOptimise your buying experience
Survey Responses/Competition Entries
Process entriesReview survey responses
Device and IP Information
Site optimisationSet default options for you (such as language and currency)Fraud/Virus protection
Anonymised session data
Improving site usabilityImproving site performance
Sharing your information
We do not, and will not, sell any of your personal data to any third party including but not limited to your name, address, email address or any payment information.
However, we share your data with the following categories of companies as an essential part of being able to provide our services to you, as set out in this statement:
Companies essential to our operations to get your purchases to you, such as payment service providers, and delivery companies
Professional service providers, such as marketing agencies, advertising partners, website hosts and CRM providers who help us run our business
Credit reference agencies, law enforcement and fraud prevention agencies
Companies approved by you, such as social media sites
We may provide third parties with aggregated but anonymised information and analytics about our customers and, before we do so, we will make sure that it does not identify you and complies with all relevant data transfer security protocols.
Marketing messages
Where you have provided explicit authorisation to do so, from time to time we'll send you marketing messages via email, SMS, mail or other electronic devices/means to keep you aware of what we're up to and to help you see and find our products.
You can stop receiving marketing messages from us at any time. You can do this:
By clicking on the 'unsubscribe' link in any email
By contacting dataprotection@universal-textiles.com
Once you do this, we will update your profile to ensure that you don't receive further marketing messages. Please note that it might take a few days for all our systems to be updated, so you might get messages from us while we process your request.
Stopping marketing messages will not stop service communications (such as order updates)
Keeping your information
We will hold on to your information for as long as is needed to be able to provide the services to you, or (in the case of any contact you may have with our Customer Service team) for as long as is necessary to provide support-related reporting and trend analysis only.
Information will only be kept if reasonably necessary or required to meet legal or regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, prevent fraud and abuse, or enforce our terms and conditions.
Your Rights
The right to be informed about how your personal information is being used
The right to access the personal information we hold about you
The right to request the correction of inaccurate personal information we hold about you
The right to request that we delete your data, or stop processing it or collecting it, in some circumstances
The right to stop direct marketing messages and to withdraw consent for other consent-based processing at any time
The right to request that we transfer or port elements of your data either to you or another service provider
The right to complain to your data protection regulator - in the UK, the Information Commissioner's Office (https://ico.org.uk/)
If you want to exercise your rights, have a complaint, or just have questions, please contact us at dataprotection@universal-textiles.com
Cookies
We use cookies to ensure that you get the most out of our site. Cookies are small text files which we store on the device you use to access the site. Cookies allow us to monitor your use of the software and simplify your use of the site. For example, a temporary cookie is also used to keep track of your "session".
For more information on cookies, please see our cookie policy.
Links to other websites
This privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit.
Changes to this policy
We keep our privacy notice under regular review. This privacy notice was last updated 13th August 2019.
Contact Us
Data ProtectionUniversal Textiles UK Ltd50 Oswin RoadLeicesterLE3 1HRUnited KingdomPhone: +44 116 218 2188Fax: +44 116 218 2198Email: dataprotection@universal-textiles.com
sign up for exclusivediscount vouchers
Error is added to your shopping cart.Continue shoppingview Cart
